do I have 1 bra on or do I not have a bra on
what do you think I have a bra on
so blatant simple
these are bras
which are made especially for backless tops
I am simply flabbergasted
because I have such tops and dresses for example
not so gladly dressed
because then I just did not have the stop here and I the
was not always confident enough to wear this
i did not always want to wear nippets
but here you have a bra now
which is just so low
that you can not see the
for backless tops
and you really only have this one band here
here you also have only these narrow bands
who are so far on the side
so really really crass I just love it
so i am so happy that i found them
I have also marked them here
they are not expensive at all
I think they cost euros or so per piece
if not cheaper
and yes then we can this summer and spring
still rock backless dresses and tops
I am so happy
so snap in any case if you want that too